RG 023, State Teachers' Retirement Board
Connecticut State Library
State Teachers' Retirement Board records
1917-1968
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut. State Teachers' Retirement Board
97 cubic feet
The State Teachers' Retirement Board administers the Teacher’s Retirement System that provides members, public school teachers and their beneficiaries, with retirement, disability, survivorship, and health benefits.
RG023
Multiple
Historical Note
The General Assembly established the teachers' retirement system by creating the Teachers' Retirement Association and it's governing body, the Teachers' Retirement Board. The legislature sought to improve the public school system's efficiency by removing mentally or physically incapacitated teachers. Successive legislatures recognized changing social patterns by amending the system to include survivorship/dependency benefits and to provide cost of living adjustments to retired teachers. The retirement systems' financial strength has become an important component in recruiting new teachers today.
The original system applied to all first time teachers entering public school systems after September 1, 1917. Teachers already employed could join the system voluntarily. The only exceptions were New London and New Haven, which had existing local retirement provisions. New London joined the system in 1919 and the General Assembly added New Haven on September 1, 1947.
From 1917 until 1979, the Teachers Retirement Board consisted of five members: three ex-officio and two elected from the association's membership. The ex-officio members were the Insurance Commissioner, the Commissioner of Education and the Banking Commissioner. In 1980, the board expanded to nine members with the addition of four publicly appointed members. In 1982, the Commissioner on Aging replaced the Banking Commissioner and an elected teacher replaced one publicly appointed member.
In 1991, the membership expanded again to its current membership of twelve. Members include the Insurance Commissioner, the Commissioner on Aging, the Commissioner of Education, three active teachers and two retired teachers elected by the membership to four year terms and four gubernatorial appointees. Members only receive reimbursement for duty-related expenses. In addition to managing the teachers' retirement system, the board's responsibilities include establishing policies, promulgating rules and regulations to carry out relevant provisions of the law, evaluating proposed legislation, reviewing members' appeals of administrative decisions, determining benefit allowances, and maintaining financial records.
See also the.
Scope and Content
Consists of information used by the Teachers' Retirement Board to determine benefits for individual teachers. Includes bound annual staffing reports listing individual teachers on a town payroll as of October 1st of a given year. The annual deduction reports list contributions made to the fund by individual teachers during the school year. The correspondence between board staff and individual teachers and school boards regarding policy decisions and procedures. The refund check registers list withdrawals made by individual teachers.
Arrangement
Series 1. Annual Staffing Reports, 1917-1968, 10 cubic feet.
Accession: 1994-034, 3 cubic feet
Accession: 1997-026, 4 cubic feet
Accession: 2009-003, 3 cubic feet
Series 2. Annual Retirement Deductions, 1917-1966, 74 cubic feet.
Accession: 1994-034, 29 cubic feet
Accession: 1997-026, 36 cubic feet
Accession: 2009-003, 9 cubic feet
Series 3. Correspondence, 1940-1950, Accession: 1994-034, 7 cubic feet.
Series 4. Refund Check Registers, 1931-1966, Accession: 2009-003, 6 cubic feet.
Related Material
None
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut. State Teachers' Retirement Board
Subjects:
Connecticut. State Teachers' Retirement Board -- Records and correspondence; Retired teachers -- Pensions -- Connecticut
Occupations:
Teachers
Document Types:
Correspondence; Personnel records
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Container List
- Series 1. Annual Staffing Reports, 1917-1968; 10 cubic feet
  - 1994-034, 3 cubic feet
    - 1917-1927, 11 volumes (Box 1)
    - 1928-1936, 9 volumes (Box 2)
    - 1937-1944, 8 volumes (Box 3)
  - 1997-026, 4 cubic feet
    - 1945-1953, 8 volumes (Box 40)
    - 1954-1958, 5 volumes (Box 41)
    - 1959-1962, 4 volumes (Box 42)
    - 1962-1963, 1 volume (Box 43)
    - Personal Payments, 1957-1963; 5 volumes (Box 43)
  - 2009-003, 3 cubic feet
    - Andover - New Hartford, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - New Haven - Woodstock Academy, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Andover - New Hartford, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - New Haven - Woodstock Academy, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Andover - Hartford, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Hartland - Ridgefield, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Rocky Hill - Woodstock Academy, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Box 1)
    - Andover - Hartford, 1966-1967; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Hartland - Ridgefield, 1966-1967; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Rocky Hill - Woodstock Academy, 1966-1967; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Andover - Hartford, 1967-1968; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Hartland - Ridgefield, 1967-1968; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Rocky Hill - Woodstock Academy, 1967-1968; 1 volume (Box 2)
    - Personal Payments, 1963-1968; 5 volumes (Box 3)
- Series 2. Annual Retirement Deductions, 1917-1966; 74 cubic feet
  - 1994-034, 29 cubic feet
    - Andover-Woodbury, 1917; 1 volume (Box 4)
    - Andover-Haddam, 1918; 1 volume (Box 4)
    - Haddam-Plainfield, 1918; 1 volume (Box 4)
    - Plainfield-Woodstock, 1918; 1 volume (Box 4)
    - Andover-Guilford, 1919; 1 volume (Box 5)
    - Haddam-Plainfield, 1919; 1 volume (Box 5)
    - Plainville-Woodstock, 1919; 1 volume (Box 5)
    - Andover-Hamden, 1920; 1 volume (Box 5)
    - Hamden-Plainville, 1920; 1 volume (Box 6)
    - Plainville-Woodstock, 1920; 1 volume (Box 6)
    - Andover-Hamden, 1921; 1 volume (Box 6)
    - Hamden-Plainfield, 1921; 1 volume (Box 7)
    - Plainville-Woodstock, 1921; 1 volume (Box 7)
    - Andover-Hamden, 1922; 1 volume (Box 7)
    - Hamden-Plainfield, 1922; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Plainville-Woodstock, 1922; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Andover-Hamden, 1923; 1 volume (Box 8)
    - Hamden-Plainfield, 1923; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Plainville-Woodstock, 1923; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Andover-Haddam, 1924; 1 volume (Box 9)
    - Haddam-Plainfield, 1924; 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Plainfield-Woodstock, 1924; 1 volume (Box 10)
    - Andover-East Lyme, 1925; 1 volume (Box 10)
    - East Lyme-Middlebury, 1925; 1 volume (Box 11)
    - Middlebury-Southbury, 1925; 1 volume (Box 11)
    - Southbury-Woodstock, 1925; 1 volume (Box 11)
    - Andover-East Lyme, 1926; 1 volume (Box 11)
    - East Lyme-Middlebury, 1926; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Middlebury-Southbury, 1926; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Southbury-Woodstock, 1926; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - Andover-East Lyme, 1927; 1 volume (Box 12)
    - East Lyme-Middlebury, 1927; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Middlebury-Southbury, 1927; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Southbury-Woodstock, 1927; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - Andover-East Lyme, 1928; 1 volume (Box 13)
    - East Lyme-Middlebury, 1928; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Middlebury-Southbury, 1928; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Southbury-Woodstock, 1928; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Andover-Eastford, 1929; 1 volume (Box 14)
    - Eastford-Lebanon, 1929; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Lebanon-Plainfield, 1929; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Plainfield-Union, 1929; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Union-Woodstock, 1929; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Andover-Durham, 1930; 1 volume (Box 15)
    - Eastford-Killingworth, 1930; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Lebanon-Oxford, 1930; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Plainfield-Trumbull, 1930; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Union-Woodstock, 1930; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Andover-Durham, 1931; 1 volume (Box 16)
    - Eastford-Killingworth, 1931; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Lebanon-Oxford, 1931; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Plainfield-Trumbull, 1931; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Union-Woodstock, 1931; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Andover-Durham, 1932; 1 volume (Box 17)
    - Eastford-Killingworth, 1932; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Lebanon-Norwich Free Academy, 1932; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Old Lyme-Trumbull, 1932; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Union-Woodstock, 1932; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Andover-Durham, 1933; 1 volume (Box 18)
    - Eastford-Killingworth, 1933; 1 volume (Box 19)
    - Lebanon-Norwich Free Academy, 1933; 1 volume (Box 19)
    - Old Lyme-Trumbull, 1933; 1 volume (Box 19)
    - Union-Woodstock, 1933; 1 volume (Box 19)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1934; 1 volume (Box 19)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1934; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1934; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - New London-Stamford, 1934; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - State Board-Woodstock, 1934; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1935; 1 volume (Box 20)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1935; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1935; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - New London-Stamford, 1935; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - State Board-Woodstock, 1935; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1936; 1 volume (Box 21)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1936; 1 volume (Box 22)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1936; 1 volume (Box 22)
    - New London-Stamford, 1936; 1 volume (Box 22)
    - State Board-Woodstock, 1936; 1 volume (Box 22)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1937; 1 volume (Box 22)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1937; 1 volume (Box 23)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1937; 1 volume (Box 23)
    - New London-Stamford, 1937; 1 volume (Box 23)
    - State Board-Woodstock, 1937; 1 volume (Box 23)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1938; 1 volume (Box 23)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1938; 1 volume (Box 24)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1938; 1 volume (Box 24)
    - New London-Stamford, 1938; 1 volume (Box 24)
    - State Board-Woodstock, 1938; 1 volume (Box 24)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1939; 1 volume (Box 24)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1939; 1 volume (Box 25)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1939; 1 volume (Box 25)
    - New London-Stamford, 1939; 1 volume (Box 25)
    - State Board-Woodstock, 1939; 1 volume (Box 25)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1940; 1 volume (Box 26)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1940; 1 volume (Box 26)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1940; 1 volume (Box 26)
    - New London-Stamford, 1940; 1 volume (Box 26)
    - State Board-Woodstock Academy, 1940; 1 volume (Box 26)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1941; 1 volume (Box 27)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1941; 1 volume (Box 27)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1941; 1 volume (Box 27)
    - New London-Stamford, 1941; 1 volume (Box 27)
    - State Board-Woodstock Academy, 1941; 1 volume (Box 27)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1942; 1 volume (Box 28)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1942; 1 volume (Box 28)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1942; 1 volume (Box 28)
    - New London-Stamford, 1942; 1 volume (Box 28)
    - State Board-Woodstock Academy, 1942; 1 volume (Box 28)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1943; 1 volume (Box 29)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1943; 1 volume (Box 29)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1943; 1 volume (Box 29)
    - New London-Stamford, 1943; 1 volume (Box 29)
    - State Board-Woodstock Academy, 1943; 1 volume (Box 29)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1944; 1 volume (Box 30)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1944; 1 volume (Box 30)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1944; 1 volume (Box 30)
    - New London-Stamford, 1944; 1 volume (Box 30)
    - State Board-Woodstock Academy, 1944; 1 volume (Box 31)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1945; 1 volume (Box 31)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1945; 1 volume (Box 31)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1945; 1 volume (Box 32)
    - New London-Stamford, 1945; 1 volume (Box 32)
    - State Board-Woodstock Academy, 1945; 1 volume (Box 32)
  - 1997-026, 36 cubic feet
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1946; 1 volume (Box 44)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1946; 1 volume (Box 44)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1946; 1 volume (Box 44)
    - New London-Stamford, 1946; 1 volume (Box 44)
    - State Board-Woodstock Academy, 1946; 1 volume (Box 45)
    - Andover-Cornwall, 1947 January-June; 1 volume (Box 45)
    - County Home-Hampton, 1947 January-June; 1 volume (Box 45)
    - Hartford-Newington, 1947 January-June; 1 volume (Box 45)
    - New London-Stamford, 1947 January-June; 1 volume (Box 45)
    - State Board-Woodstock Academy, 1947 January-June; 1 volume (Box 45)
    - Andover-Essex Pratt High School, 1947 July-December; 1 volume (Box 46)
    - Fairfield-Morris, 1947 July-December; 1 volume (Box 46)
    - Naugatuck-Stafford, 1947 July-December; 1 volume (Box 46)
    - Stamford-Woodstock Academy, 1947 July-December; 1 volume (Box 46)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1948; 1 volume (Box 46)
    - Canaan-Essex Pratt High School, 1948; 1 volume (Box 47)
    - Fairfield-Hampton, 1948; 1 volume (Box 47)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1948; 1 volume (Box 47)
    - Milford-Newington, 1948; 1 volume (Box 47)
    - New London-Seymour, 1948; 1 volume (Box 47)
    - Sharon-Voluntown, 1948; 1 volume (Box 48)
    - Wallingford-Woodstock Academy, 1948; 1 volume (Box 48)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1949; 1 volume (Box 48)
    - Canaan-Essex, 1949; 1 volume (Box 48)
    - Fairfield-Hampton, 1949; 1 volume (Box 49)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1949; 1 volume (Box 49)
    - Milford-Newington, 1949; 1 volume (Box 49)
    - New London-Seymour, 1949; 1 volume (Box 49)
    - Sharon-Voluntown, 1949; 1 volume (Box 49)
    - Wallingford-Woodstock, 1949; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1950; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - Canaan-Essex Pratt High School, 1950; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - Fairfield-Hampton, 1950; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1950; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - Milford-New Hartford, 1950; 1 volume (Box 50)
    - New Haven, 1950; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Newington-Putnam, 1950; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1950; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - State Board-Waterbury, 1950; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1950; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1951; 1 volume (Box 51)
    - Canaan-Essex, 1951; 1 volume (Box 52)
    - Fairfield-Hampton, 1951; 1 volume (Box 52)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1951; 1 volume (Box 52)
    - Milford-New Hartford, 1951; 1 volume (Box 52)
    - New Haven, 1951; 1 volume (Box 52)
    - Newington-Putnam, 1951; 1 volume (Box 52)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1951; 1 volume (Box 53)
    - State Board-Waterbury, 1951; 1 volume (Box 53)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1951; 1 volume (Box 53)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1952; 1 volume (Box 53)
    - Canaan-Essex, 1952; 1 volume (Box 53)
    - Fairfield-Hampton, 1952; 1 volume (Box 53)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1952; 1 volume (Box 54)
    - Milford-New Hartford, 1952; 1 volume (Box 54)
    - New Haven, 1952; 1 volume (Box 54)
    - Newington-Putnam, 1952; 1 volume (Box 54)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1952; 1 volume (Box 54)
    - State Board-Waterbury, 1952; 1 volume (Box 54)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1952; 1 volume (Box 55)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1953; 1 volume (Box 55)
    - Canaan-Essex, 1953; 1 volume (Box 55)
    - Fairfield-Hampton, 1953; 1 volume (Box 55)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1953; 1 volume (Box 55)
    - Milford-New Hartford, 1953; 1 volume (Box 55)
    - New Haven, 1953; 1 volume (Box 56)
    - Newington-Putnam, 1953; 1 volume (Box 56)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1953; 1 volume (Box 56)
    - State Board-Waterbury, 1953; 1 volume (Box 56)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1953; 1 volume (Box 56)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1954; 1 volume (Box 57)
    - Canaan-Essex, 1954; 1 volume (Box 57)
    - Fairfield-Hampton, 1954; 1 volume (Box 57)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1954; 1 volume (Box 57)
    - Milford-New Hartford, 1954; 1 volume (Box 57)
    - New Haven, 1954; 1 volume (Box 57)
    - Newington-Putnam, 1954; 1 volume (Box 58)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1954; 1 volume (Box 58)
    - State Board-Waterbury, 1954; 1 volume (Box 58)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1954; 1 volume (Box 58)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 58)
    - Canaan-Essex, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 58)
    - Fairfield-Hampton, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 59)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 59)
    - Milford-New Haven, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 59)
    - New Haven, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 59)
    - Newington-Putnam, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 59)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 59)
    - State Board-Waterbury, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 59)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1955 January-June; 1 volume (Box 59)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 1)
    - Canaan-Easton, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 2)
    - East Windsor-Hampton, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 3)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 4)
    - Milford-North Haven, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 5)
    - North Stonington-Putnam, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 6)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 7)
    - State-Waterbury, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 9)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1955 September-1956 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 10)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 11)
    - Canaan-Easton, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 12)
    - East Windsor-Hampton, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 13)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 14)
    - Milford-North Haven, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 15)
    - North Stonington-Putnam, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 16)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 18)
    - State-Waterbury, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 19)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1956 September-1957 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 20)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1957-1958; 1 volume (Volume Volume 21)
    - Canaan-Easton, 1957 September-1958 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 22)
    - East Windsor-Hampton, 1957 September-1958 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 23)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1957 September-1959 April; 1 volume (Volume Volume 24)
    - Milford-North Haven, 1957 September-1959 April; 1 volume (Volume Volume 25)
    - North Stonington-Putnam, 1957 September-1958 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 26)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1957 September-1958 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 27)
    - State-Waterbury, 1957 July-1958 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 28)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1957 September-1958 June; 1 volume (Volume Volume 17)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 29)
    - Canaan-Easton, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 30)
    - East Windsor-Hampton, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 31)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 32)
    - Milford-North Haven, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 33)
    - North Stonington-Putnam, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 34)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 35)
    - State-Waterbury, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 36)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1958-1959; 1 volume (Volume Volume 37)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 38)
    - Canaan-Easton, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 39)
    - East Windsor-Hampton, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 40)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 41)
    - Milford-North Haven, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 42)
    - North Stonington-Putnam, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 43)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 44)
    - State-Waterbury, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 8)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1959-1960; 1 volume (Volume Volume 45)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 46)
    - Canaan-Easton, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 47)
    - East Windsor-Hampton, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 48)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 49)
    - Milford-North Haven, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 50)
    - North Stonington-Putnam, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 51)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 52)
    - State-Waterbury, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 53)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1960-1961; 1 volume (Volume Volume 54)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 55)
    - Canaan-Easton, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 56)
    - East Windsor-Hampton, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 57)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 58)
    - Milford-North Haven, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 59)
    - North Stonington-Putnam, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 60)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 61)
    - State-Waterbury, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 62)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1961-1962; 1 volume (Volume Volume 63)
    - Andover-Burlington, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 64)
    - Canaan-Easton, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 65)
    - East Windsor-Hampton, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 66)
    - Hartford-Middletown, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 67)
    - Milford-North Haven, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 68)
    - North Stonington-Putnam, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 69)
    - Redding-Stamford, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 70)
    - State-Waterbury, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 71)
    - Waterford-Woodstock Academy, 1962-1963; 1 volume (Volume Volume 72)
  - 2009-003, 9 cubic feet
    - Andover - Burlington, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 4)
    - Canaan - Easton, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 5)
    - East Windsor - Hampton, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 6)
    - Hartford - Middletown, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 7)
    - Milford - North Haven, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 8)
    - North Stonington - Putnam, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 9)
    - Redding - Stamford, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 10)
    - State Board - Waterbury, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 11)
    - Waterford - Woodstock Academy, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 12)
    - Andover - Burlington, 1963-1964; 1 volume (Volume Item 13)
    - Canaan - Easton, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Volume Item 14)
    - East Windsor - Hampton, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Volume Item 15)
    - Hartford - Middletown, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Volume Item 16)
    - Milford - North Haven, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Volume Item 17)
    - North Stonington - Putnam, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Volume Item 18)
    - Redding - Stamford, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Volume Item 19)
    - State Board - Waterbury, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Volume Item 20)
    - Waterford - Woodstock Academy, 1964-1965; 1 volume (Volume Item 21)
    - Andover - Burlington, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 22)
    - Canaan - East Hartford, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 23)
    - East Haven - Hampton, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 24)
    - Hartford - Middletown, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 25)
    - Milford - North Canaan, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 26)
    - North Haven - Region No. 5, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 27)
    - Region No. 6 - Stafford, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 28)
    - Stamford - Sterling, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 29)
    - Stonington - Watertown, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 30)
    - Westbrook - Woodstock Academy, 1965-1966; 1 volume (Volume Item 31)
- Series 3. Correspondence, 1940-1950; 1994-034; 7 cubic feet
  - Andover-Canterbury (Box 33)
  - Chester-Essex (Box 34)
  - Fairfield-Killingly (Box 35)
  - Killingworth-New London (Box 36)
  - New Haven-Scotland (Box 37)
  - Seymour-Voluntown (Box 38)
  - Wallingford-Winchester (Box 39)
- Series 4. Refund Check Registers, 1931-1966; 6 cubic feet
  - 2009-003, 6 cubic feet